designsmaz.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy - DesignMaz

At Design Maz, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by Designsmaz.com and how it is used.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us from](https://designsmaz.com/contact-us/).

## Log Files

Design Maz makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) address, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/timestamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information can be linked to information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies

On Design Maz several third-party cookies are used, such as the ones of Google Analytics and social networks.  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web bugs on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

## Third-party ad servers

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on **Design Maz  **send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web bugs) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Design Maz has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Designmaz’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

 **If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.** More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
